<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
    SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2020 Elvis Angelaccio <elvis.angelaccio@kde.org>
-->
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kio_s3</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.gwenview.desktop</extends>
  <name>KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KIO S3</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKIO S3xx</name>
  <summary>Amazon S3 integration with KDE Plasma and KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Integració de l'Amazon S3 amb el Plasma del KDE i les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Integració de l'Amazon S3 amb el Plasma del KDE i les aplicacions KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Amazon S3 integration with KDE Plasma and KDE applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Integración de Amazon S3 con Plasma de KDE y aplicaciones de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">L'intégration de « Amazon S3 » avec KDE Plasma et les applications Plasma.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Amazon S3 integratie met KDE Plasma en KDE toepassingen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Integrering av Amazon S3 med KDE Plasma og KDE-programma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Amazon S3 integracija s KDE Plasma s KDE aplikacijami</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Amazon S3 integrering med KDE Plasma och KDE program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інтеграція Amazon S3 із Плазмою KDE та програмами KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxAmazon S3 integration with KDE Plasma and KDE applicationsxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KIO S3 enables KIO-aware applications (such as Dolphin, Kate or Gwenview) to access and edit Amazon S3 buckets and objects.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KIO S3 és un esclau del KIO que permet a les aplicacions preparades per al KIO (com el Dolphin, el Kate o el Gwenview) que accedeixin i editin els dipòsits i objectes d'Amazon S3.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KIO S3 és un esclau del KIO que permet a les aplicacions preparades per al KIO (com el Dolphin, el Kate o el Gwenview) que accedisquen i editin els dipòsits i objectes d'Amazon S3.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KIO S3 enables KIO-aware applications (such as Dolphin, Kate or Gwenview) to access and edit Amazon S3 buckets and objects.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KIO S3 permite a las aplicaciones que usan KIO (como Dolphin, Kate o Gwenview) acceder y editar buckets y objetos de Amazon S3.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KIO S3 active les applications compatibles avec « KIO » (comme Dolphin, Kate et Gwenview) pour accéder et modifier des conteneurs et objets « Amazon S3 ».</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KIO S3 schakelt toepassingen in die afweten van KIO (zoals Dolphin, Kate of Gwenview) om Amazon S3 buckets en objects te benaderen en te bewerken.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KIO S3 lèt program som brukar KIO (for eksempel Dolphin, Kate og Gwenview) få lese- og skrivetilgang til «buckets» og objekt på Amazon S3.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KIO S3 omogoča aplikacijam, ki se zavedajo KIO (kot so Dolphin, Kate ali Gwenview) dostop in urejanje segmentov in predmetov Amazon S3.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KIO S3 gör det möjligt för program som känner till KIO (såsom Dolphin, Kate eller Gwenview) att komma åt och redigera Amazon S3 spannar och objekt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KIO S3 надає змогу програмам, які використовують KIO (зокрема Dolphin, Kate та Gwenview) отримувати доступ до кошиків та об'єктів Amazon S3 та редагувати дані у них.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKIO S3 enables KIO-aware applications (such as Dolphin, Kate or Gwenview) to access and edit Amazon S3 buckets and objects.xx</p>
  </description>
  <!--  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/en/kio_s3</url>-->
  <!--  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kio-s3</url>-->
  <!--   <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kioslave5%2Fs3</url> -->
  <update_contact>elvis.angelaccio_at_kde.org</update_contact>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Dolphin showing a picture uploaded on an Amazon S3 bucket.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">El Dolphin mostrant una imatge carregada sobre un dipòsit d'Amazon S3.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Dolphin mostrant una imatge carregada sobre un dipòsit d'Amazon S3.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Dolphin showing a picture uploaded on an Amazon S3 bucket.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Dolphin mostrando una imagen enviada a un bucket de Amazon S3.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Dolphin affichant une image envoyée vers un conteneur « Amazon S3 ».</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Dolphin die een op een Amazon S3 bucket geüploade afbeelding toont.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Dolphin som viser eit bilete lasta på til ei Amazon S3-«bucket».</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Delfin prikazuje sliko naloženo v vedro Amazon S3.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Dolphin showing som visar en bild uppladdad till en Amazon S3 spann.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Знімок вікна Dolphin із вивантаженням даних до кошика Amazon S3.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxDolphin showing a picture uploaded on an Amazon S3 bucket.xx</caption>
      <image type="source" width="1494" height="825">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kio-s3/kio-s3.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <!--  <releases>
    <release version="20.08.1" date="2020-09-03"/>
  </releases>-->
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">folder-network</icon>
</component>
